Life is a journey full of possibilities
and every decision we make shapes our
future.
We need to choose the path that leads to
more. More financial security, more
wealth creation, and more value for
money for a brighter tomorrow.
Presenting ICICI Pro Signature, a unit
linked life insurance plan that is
designed to give you more in every
aspect of your financial journey. Its
numerous benefits make it an incredible
choice. Unlock the potential of
marketdriven returns. Wealth boosters to
boost your investments.
Life cover to safeguard the financial
future of your family. Return of premium
allocation charges to save more. Choice
of four portfolio strategies
with a wide range of funds.
Enjoy policy benefits till the age of 99
with the whole life policy term.
Systematic withdrawal plans for regular
payouts. Top up option for additional
savings and tax benefits.
So let's see how this plan works. Meet
Mr. Akshai, a 40-year-old IT
professional. He wishes to create
wealth.
So he selects the ICICI pro signature
plan.
In case of his death during the policy
term, Akshai's family or nominee will
receive the life cover ICICI proof
signature. A plan that helps you achieve
more.